PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated professional with experience in customer service and culinary arts. Engaging rapport building: effective in building productive working relationships based on helpfulness, professionalism, integrity, reliability, and trust. Thoughtful, balanced, problem solver with a customer service focus. Value-added performer with a take-charge attitude, strong work ethic and reputation for rising to the challenge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Uncle Leos Pizza, St Louis MO - July 2023 to present day

-Line cook: responsible for all aspects of food production and ensuring product is prepared in a safe and efficient manner for all customers.

Friendship Village, Sunset Hills MO – June 2018 to April 2024

- Kitchen Lead: responsible for all aspects of food production, working with chefs to write menus and daily specials. Leading each dinner shift to ensure that each dish is prepared correctly and fast as possible. Working expo alongside front of house.

UniGroup/United Van Lines, Fenton MO - March 2017 to June 2018

-Transportation Specialist and dispatcher: communicating with drivers to ensure shipments arrive on time and undamaged. Managing my driver's routes and weekly truckloads.

Grand Slam Bar and Grill, Fenton MO – October 2017 to October 2018

- Line Cook: responsible for all aspects of food production, prep, grill and sauté.

Bella Vino Wine and Tapas Bar, St Charles MO – April 2016 to October 2016

- Prep cook: prepare food for line cooks, maintain a well-stocked and clean kitchen

EDUCATION

Ranken Technical College, St Louis MO, - August 2024 to present day

-Web and App Development

Southeast Missouri State University, Cape Girardeau, MO – August 2010 – July 2012

-Studio and Graphic Arts

Jefferson College, Hillsboro, MO – August 2008 – July 2010

-General Studies